Connecticut	LOCATION
school	LOCATION
shooting	O
:	O
AP	O
...	O
SearchImagesMapsPlayYouTubeNewsGmailDriveMoreCalendarTranslateMobileBooksOffersWalletShoppingBloggerReaderFinancePhotosVideosEven	O
more	O
''	O
Account	O
OptionsSign	O
inSettingsSearch	O
settingsWeb	O
History	O
News	O
Top	O
StoriesNews	O
near	O
youWorldU.S.BusinessTechnologyEntertainmentSportsScienceHealthSpotlightTop	O
StoriesNews	O
near	O
youWorldU.S.BusinessTechnologyEntertainmentSportsScienceHealthSpotlightSearch	O
this	O
story	O
All	O
news	O
ArticlesSorted	O
by	O
relevance	O
Sorted	O
by	O
date	O
Reset	O
options	O
Full	O
coverage	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
school	LOCATION
shooting	O
:	O
AP	O
source	O
:	O
Suspect	O
is	O
Ryan	PERSON
Lanza	PERSON
,	O
24	O
;	O
younger	O
...	O
Politico	O
-	O
22	O
hours	O
ago	O
WASHINGTON	LOCATION
--	O
The	O
suspect	O
in	O
the	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
school	LOCATION
shootings	O
is	O
Adam	PERSON
Lanza	PERSON
,	O
20	O
,	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
a	O
teacher	O
at	O
the	O
school	LOCATION
where	O
the	O
shootings	O
occurred	O
,	O
a	O
law	O
enforcement	O
official	O
said	O
Friday	TIME
.	O
A	O
second	O
law	O
enforcement	O
official	O
says	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
Nancy	PERSON
...	O
Hundreds	O
pack	O
Conn.	LOCATION
churches	O
after	O
rampage	O
Detroit	LOCATION
Free	O
Press	O
-	O
13	O
hours	O
ago	O
Men	O
and	O
women	O
hold	O
candles	O
in	O
vigil	O
outside	O
St.	O
Rose	O
of	O
Lima	O
Roman	O
Catholic	O
Church	O
during	O
a	O
healing	O
service	O
for	O
victims	O
of	O
the	O
elementary	O
school	LOCATION
shooting	O
in	O
Newtown	LOCATION
,	O
Conn.	LOCATION
,	O
on	O
Friday	TIME
.	O
/	O
Charles	PERSON
Krupa	PERSON
,	O
AP	O
.	O
USA	O
Today	O
...	O
ID	O
mix-up	O
of	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
shooter	O
,	O
brother	O
prompts	O
plea	O
:	O
`	O
It	O
was	O
n't	O
me	O
'	O
Detroit	LOCATION
Free	O
Press	O
-	O
5	O
hours	O
ago	O
The	O
suspect	O
in	O
the	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
shooting	O
,	O
Adam	PERSON
Lanza	PERSON
,	O
20	O
,	O
was	O
apparently	O
carrying	O
his	O
older	O
brother	O
Ryan	PERSON
's	O
identification	O
,	O
setting	O
off	O
a	O
media	O
mixup	O
that	O
propelled	O
Ryan	PERSON
's	O
Facebook	O
photo	O
onto	O
the	O
Internet	O
tens	O
of	O
thousands	O
of	O
times	O
as	O
the	O
purported	O
shooter	O
...	O
AP	O
Source	O
:	O
Some	O
of	O
weapons	O
used	O
in	O
Conn.	LOCATION
rampage	O
match	O
models	O
of	O
guns	O
...	O
Washington	LOCATION
Post	O
-	O
14	O
hours	O
ago	O
WASHINGTON	LOCATION
--	O
A	O
law	O
enforcement	O
official	O
says	O
some	O
guns	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
the	O
gunman	O
in	O
the	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
elementary	O
school	LOCATION
rampage	O
match	O
the	O
models	O
of	O
the	O
guns	O
used	O
in	O
the	O
shooting	O
.	O
The	O
official	O
cautions	O
that	O
investigators	O
have	O
n't	O
conclusively	O
...	O
Shooter	O
forced	O
his	O
way	O
into	O
Newtown	LOCATION
school	LOCATION
,	O
investigators	O
say	O
Torrington	LOCATION
Register	O
Citizen	O
-	O
2	O
hours	O
ago	O
NEWTOWN	LOCATION
--	O
The	O
massacre	O
of	O
26	O
children	O
and	O
adults	O
at	O
a	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
elementary	O
school	LOCATION
elicited	O
horror	O
and	O
soul-searching	O
around	O
the	O
world	O
even	O
as	O
it	O
raised	O
more	O
basic	O
questions	O
about	O
why	O
the	O
gunman	O
,	O
a	O
20-year-old	O
described	O
as	O
brilliant	O
but	O
remote	O
,	O
was	O
...	O
Obama	PERSON
statement	O
on	O
the	O
school	O
shooting	O
in	O
Newtown	LOCATION
Conn.	LOCATION
.	O
Kansas	LOCATION
City	LOCATION
Star	O
-	O
21	O
hours	O
ago	O
More	O
News	O
.	O
THE	O
WHITE	O
HOUSE	O
Office	O
of	O
the	O
Press	O
Secretary	O
.	O
For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
December	O
14	O
,	O
2012	O
.	O
STATEMENT	O
BY	O
THE	O
PRESIDENT	O
ON	O
SCHOOL	LOCATION
SHOOTING	O
IN	O
NEWTOWN	LOCATION
,	O
CONNECTICUT	LOCATION
.	O
James	O
S.	O
Brady	O
Press	O
Briefing	O
Room	O
.	O
3:15	O
P.M.	O
EST	O
...	O
Plymouth	LOCATION
Schools	LOCATION
Superintendent	O
Addresses	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
School	LOCATION
Shooting	O
Patch.com	ORGANIZATION
-	O
2	O
hours	O
ago	O
Editor	O
's	O
note	O
:	O
Superintendent	O
of	O
Schools	O
,	O
Dr.	O
Gary	PERSON
E.	O
Maestas	PERSON
,	O
sent	O
out	O
a	O
letter	O
via	O
Twitter	ORGANIZATION
to	O
the	O
community	O
on	O
Friday	TIME
responding	O
to	O
the	O
shootings	O
at	O
Sandy	LOCATION
Hook	LOCATION
Elementary	O
School	LOCATION
in	O
Newtown	LOCATION
,	O
CT.	LOCATION
.	O
The	O
full	O
text	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
follows	O
:	O
Dear	O
Parents	O
and	O
...	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
police	O
respond	O
to	O
reports	O
of	O
elementary	O
school	LOCATION
shooting	O
The	O
Guardian	O
-	O
Dec	TIME
14	TIME
,	O
2012	O
Police	O
are	O
on	O
the	O
scene	O
at	O
an	O
elementary	LOCATION
school	O
in	O
Newtown	LOCATION
,	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
,	O
following	O
reports	O
of	O
a	O
shooting	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
prompted	O
the	O
lockdown	O
of	O
all	O
pupils	O
and	O
teachers	O
across	O
the	O
district	O
.	O
A	O
spokeswoman	O
for	O
the	O
Newtown	LOCATION
public	O
school	O
district	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
...	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
School	LOCATION
Shooting	O
:	O
Suspected	O
shooter	O
now	O
ID	O
'd	O
as	O
Adam	PERSON
Lanza	PERSON
...	O
CBS	O
News	O
-	O
21	O
hours	O
ago	O
-LRB-	O
AP	O
-RRB-	O
WASHINGTON	LOCATION
-	O
A	O
law	O
enforcement	O
official	O
says	O
the	O
shooter	O
in	O
the	O
Newtown	LOCATION
,	O
Conn.	LOCATION
school	LOCATION
massacre	O
is	O
20-year-old	O
Adam	PERSON
Lanza	PERSON
,	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
a	O
teacher	O
at	O
Sandy	O
Hook	O
Elementary	O
School	LOCATION
where	O
the	O
bloodbath	O
occurred	O
.	O
A	O
second	O
law	O
enforcement	O
official	O
...	O
UPDATE	O
:	O
Latest	O
on	O
the	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
school	LOCATION
shooting	O
|	O
WTVR.com	O
--	O
Richmond	O
...	O
WTVR	O
-	O
2	O
hours	O
ago	O
-LRB-	O
CNN	ORGANIZATION
-RRB-	O
--	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
State	O
Police	O
held	O
a	O
news	O
conference	O
Saturday	TIME
morning	O
to	O
update	O
the	O
public	O
about	O
the	O
investigation	O
into	O
the	O
mass	O
shooting	O
at	O
Sandy	LOCATION
Hook	LOCATION
Elementary	O
School	LOCATION
in	O
Newtown	O
,	O
Connecticut	LOCATION
.	O
Police	O
spokesman	O
Lt.	O
J.	O
Paul	PERSON
Vance	PERSON
offered	O
the	O
...	O
Gov	O
,	O
gov-elect	O
express	O
sympathy	O
for	O
Conn	LOCATION
victims	O
Boston.com	ORGANIZATION
-	O
21	O
hours	O
ago	O
CONCORD	O
,	O
N.H.	O
-LRB-	O
AP	O
-RRB-	O
--	O
New	LOCATION
Hampshire	LOCATION
's	O
governor	O
and	O
governor-elect	O
are	O
expressing	O
sympathy	O
for	O
the	O
victims	O
of	O
a	O
shooting	O
at	O
a	O
Newtown	LOCATION
,	O
Conn.	LOCATION
,	O
elementary	O
school	LOCATION
